Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series II. Clients J-P
  - Massey, Jr. Location: Unspecified
    - First floor plan and landscape plan about House, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1198
    - Sketch of side elevation, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1199
    - Sketch of floor plan and furnishings, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1200
    - Sketch of elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1201
    - Rough sketch of drives, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1202
    - Basement plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1203
    - Attic and third floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1204
    - Sketch - elevation, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1205
      Condition:Poor - Part of sketch is missing
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1206
    - Rough sketch of house and entry plan, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1207
    - Sketch of second floor plan and furnishing, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1208
  - McIntosh, Mrs. H. D. Location: Binghamton
    - Plan and section of wall, garden, 1917 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1666
  - Client: McIntosh, H. P., Jr. Location: Bratenahl, Ohio
    - Living room details, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1631
      Note:By Meade & Hamilton
    - Living room details, 1916 (Box 49)
      Sheet # 1632
    - Details, 1916 (Folder 56)
      Sheet # 1633
    - Sun porch details, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1634
    - Dining room details, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1635
    - Details of bedroom "A", 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1636
    - Residence, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1637
    - South elevation, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1638
    - Rear elevation, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1639
    - North elevation, 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1640
    - Section toward South, etc, c. 1916 (Box 56)
      Sheet # 1641
    - Basement level plan, 1916 (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1642
    - First floor plan, 1916 (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1643
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1644
    - Third floor and roof plan, Undated (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1645
    - Main stair details, Undated (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1646
    - Main stair details, 1916 (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1647
    - Main stair details, Undated (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1648
    - Main stair details, 1916 (Box 57)
      Sheet # 1649
    - Planting plan, 1918 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 1658
    - Arbor, 1918 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1659
    - Detail of platform at Beech tree, 1918 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1660
    - Sketch plan of arrangement, 1917 (Folder 49)
      Sheet # 1693
    - Dimensional general plan of arrangement, 1917 (Folder 49)
      Sheet # 1694
  - Client: McIntosh, H. P. Location: Bratenahl, Ohio
    - Full scale detail of seat and platform round beech, 1918 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1725
  - McKinney, L. C. Location: Titusville, Pennsylvania
    - Library cabinet drawings - Hyde Murphy Co., 1927 (Folder 11)
      Sheet # 124
      Format: Blueprint, Oversized
    - Library cabinet drawings - Hyde Murphy Co., 1927 (Folder 11)
      Sheet # 125
    - List of landscape drawings sent out, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 862
    - Dimensions on Parterre Gardens, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 863
    - Dimensional revisions - east end of breakfast room terrace, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 864
    - Notes and Sketches of dimensions for construction, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 865
    - Notes and measurements for blinds, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 866
    - Construction notes, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 867
    - Measurements for construction, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 868
    - Sketches of garden details, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 869
    - Sketches of brick patterns, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 870
    - Birds-eye view of proposed garden development, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 871
    - View on main axis looking towards swimming pool and casino, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 872
    - Sketch detail of sinks for Butler's pantry and flower room, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 875
    - Sketch of south elevation of residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 876
    - Sketch of roofline and sleeping porch, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 878
    - Study of house: Scale drawing of west elevation, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 879
    - Scale drawing of east elevation, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 880
    - Scale drawing of south elevation, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 881
    - Perspective sketch of House, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 882
    - Two stone pedestals - plan and elevation, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 883
    - Sketch of terminal posts to south lawn, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 884
      Scale: 7'=1"
    - Bracket from Feine, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 885
    - Sketch of decorative iron work, likely, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 886
    - Plan of turf terrace garden, 1928 (Box 33)
      Sheet # 887
    - Sections of entry gates, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 888
    - Full scale detail of lower terrace coping, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 889
    - Perspective sketch of cast-iron porch, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 890
    - Sketch for stone urn, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 891
    - Perspective sketch in garden, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 892
    - View looking northwest from tennis court through Casino, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 893
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 905
    - Cellar plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 906
    - Rough sketch of site plan, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 907
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 908
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 909
    - Partial first floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 910
    - First and second floor plans, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 911
      Format: Ink on tracing paper
    - Third floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 912
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 913
    - Sketch plan of Pass-court, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 914
    - Third floor plan - New additions plus existing structure, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 915
    - Third floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 916
    - Sketch and notes on dormer windows, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 917
    - First and second floor plans, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 918
    - Scale drawing of north elevation, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 919
    - Perspective sketch of residence, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 920
    - Typical exterior elevation - Swedish venetian blinds, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 921
    - Preliminary first floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 922
    - Sketch study - Alteration to garage - West elevation, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 923
    - Sketch study - Alteration to garage - South elevation, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 924
    - Third floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 925
    - East elevation of house, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 926
    - Details for Parterre Garden, 1928 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1329
    - Details in arrival court, 1926 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1330
    - Details in arrival court, 1926 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1352
    - Library, Plan and Stone details, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1353
    - Arrival court, 1926 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1354
    - Garden and House outlines, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1355
    - Garden and House outlines, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1356
    - Garden and House outlines, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1357
  - McKinney, Price Location: Wickliffe, Ohio (or unspecified)
    - First floor, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1300
    - Topography survey, 1918 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1303
    - Sketch of property walls, 1916 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1304
    - Cross sections from old survey, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1305
    - Temporary study, residence and grounds, Undated (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1306
    - Rough sketch of residence, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1307
    - Rough sketch, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1308
    - Elevation of cottage toward entrance road, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1309
    - Alterations to sun and palm rooms, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1310
    - Sketch of living quarters (Likely Chauffers'), Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1311
    - Sketch - End of Front Yard, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1312
    - Sketch of garage, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1313
    - Topo, 1918 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1314
    - Outlines of house, Undated (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1315
    - Barn, Ground floor, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1345
    - Basement plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1346
    - Dairy and Ice House, First floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1347
    - Barn and Ice house, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1348
    - Dairy barn and Ice House, 1908 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1349
    - Dairy barn and Ice House, 1908 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1350
    - First floor plan, Residence, 1916 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1351
  - Location: Cleveland, Ohio
    - Alterations to sun room, palm room, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1301
    - Alterations to sun room, palm room, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1302
    - Alterations to sun and palm rooms, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Mengel, C. C. Location: Glenview, Kentucky
    - West elevation of residence, Undated (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1331
    - Landscape plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1332
    - Detailed landscape plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1333
    - Basement plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1334
    - First floor plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1335
    - Second floor plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1336
    - Roof plan, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1337
    - East elevation, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1338
    - South elevation, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1339
    - North elevation, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1340
    - Details of column arches, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1341
      Scale: Full; 1 1/2"=1'
    - Details of main entrance, louvres, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1342
    - Arches, alcove, living room, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1343
    - Interior details, 1921 (Box 46)
      Sheet # 1344
  - Meredith, Sir William Location: Toronto, Ontario
    - Entrance gates, 1909 (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 134
    - Detail plan about House, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 135
    - Herbaceous borders, Undated (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 136
    - Sketch for entrance gate, Undated (Box 7)
      Sheet # 137
    - Floor plans, 1909 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 138
      Note:Townsend & Fleming; Traced from GM Miller & co., Architects, Toronto
    - Entrance gates; Schemes B and C, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 139
    - Planting plan of the Terrace, 1909 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 140
    - House site - Scheme A, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 141
    - Sketch for Leaded Casement Sash, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 142
    - Planting List (Box 9)
      Sheet # 143
    - Planting List, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 144
    - House site - Scheme C, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 145
    - Suggested changes for plan of Residence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 146
    - Sketched section through residence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 147
    - Sketch for alternate garden, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 148
    - Floor plan of a portion of the residence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 149
    - House site - Scheme B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 150
    - Partial floor plan, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 151
    - Partial floor plan, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 152
    - Revised plan for planting entrance & about house, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 153
    - Plan Rider, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 154
    - Scale detail of Living room by Architects G. M. Miller & co., 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 155
    - Sketch "D" - Study of arrangement of house, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 156
    - Sketch "A" - Study of arrangement of house, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 157
    - Study about house, 1909 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 158
    - Preliminary sketch of grounds about house, 1908 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 159
    - Detail of Entrance Hall, etc., by Architects G. M. Miller & co., 1908 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 160
    - Front Entrance door, by Architects G. M. Miller & co., 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 161
    - Profiles showing grading on Estate, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 162
    - Sketch "B" - Study of arrangement of house, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 163
    - Sketch "C" - Study of arrangement of house, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 164
    - List of areas to be cut and filled, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 165
      Format: Tracing paper, Fair condition
    - Profiles showing grading on Estate, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 166
    - Profiles on roads, 1908 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 167
    - Portion of " Profiles on Road" Drawing, Undated (Box 8)
      Sheet # 168
    - Sketch of Survey Map of property, Undated (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 169
      Format: Sepia glued to heavy Construction paper
    - Arrangement of Grounds and Grading plan, 1908 (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 170
    - Arrangement of Grounds and Grading plan, 1908 (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 171
    - Planting plan of the Terrace, Undated (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 172
    - Topographic survey of property, 1907 (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 173
    - Planting plan, 1909 (Folder 13)
      Sheet # 174
    - Profiles of Roads, 1908 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 182
      Format: Gridded Tracing paper, Good condition
    - Profiles of Roads, 1907 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 183
    - Plans and Sections for Proposed Residence, by Architects G.M. Miller & Co., Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 184
    - Elevations of Proposed Residence, by Architects G.M. Miller & Co., Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 185
    - Arrangement for Property, 1907 (Folder 13)
      Sheet # 186
      Format: Blueprint, Fair condition
    - Elevations of Proposed Residence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 280
    - Topographical survey, 1908 (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 281
    - Profile of roads, 1908 (Box 14)
      Sheet # 282
    - Ground plan, 1907 (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 283
  - Metcalf, George A. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Enlarged survey of property, 1918 (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1212
      Format: Heavy construction -type paper, likely
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1726
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1727
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1728
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1729
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1730
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1731
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1732
    - Rough drawings - TP 17, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1733
    - Study of sub division, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1747
    - Study of sub division, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1748
    - Study of sub division, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1749
    - Study of sub division, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1750
  - Miner, F. B. Location: Flint, Michigan
    - Plan for development of property, 1927 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1404
    - Landscape arrangement, 1927 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1405
      Scale: Scale: 1"=20'
  - The Morley's Adirondacks Hotels Company/Morley Adirondack Hotel Company Location: Lake Pleasant, New York
    - Elevations and plans of Hotel, 1916 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 999
      Note:By architect Howard F. Daly
    - Elevations and plans of Hotel, 1916 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 1000
    - Revised basement plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1001
    - South and North elevation of hotel, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1002
    - Second floor plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1003
    - Third floor plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1004
    - Section and details, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1005
    - Grade elevations of site, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1006
    - East elevation, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1007
    - Foundation plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1008
    - Roof plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1009
    - First floor plan, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1010
    - Rough sketch of terrace, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1011
    - Perspective sketch of arbor, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1012
    - Plan sketch with some grading measurements, Undated (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 1013
    - Perspective sketch of hotel and arbor walkway, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1014
    - Rough plan for entry, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1015
    - Perspective sketch of hotel and arbor walkway, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1016
    - Rough sketches for landscape, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1017
    - Rough sketches in garden, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1018
    - Sign posts for Hotel, 1917 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 1019
    - Detail of supports and lighting - Signposts, 1917 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 1020
    - Signboard for Hotel, 1917 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 1021
    - Perspective showing landscape development, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1022
    - Sketch section and elevation for landscape development, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1023
    - Sketch plan showing landscape development, Undated (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 1024
    - Signboards for the Hotel, 1917 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1025
      Format: Heavy Paper, likely
    - Diagram of Tennis courts, 1917 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1026
    - Topographical survey of property, 1916 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1027
    - Profile of entrance drive, 1917 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1028
      Format: Gridded profile paper
    - Sketch for arbor at tap and wine room entrance with attached notes, 1917 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1029
      Format: Tracing paper and Note paper
    - Arbor plan and section, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1030
    - Detail of Arbor, 1917 (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1031
    - Plan of Hotel showing location of lights, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1032
    - Staking plan, Undated (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1033
    - Sketch for Arbor at tap and wine room entrance, Undated (Box 36)
      Sheet # 1034
    - Signboards for Hotel, 1917 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1035
    - Detail of entrance court, Undated (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1036
    - Staking plan of service road, 1917 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1037
  - Myers, P. A. Location: Ashland, Ohio
    - Plan of pool and paved area, 1/2" scale details of garden, 1915 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 284
    - Plan and details for main terrace, 1915 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 285
    - Plan and details for Southeast terrace and drive, Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 286
    - Detail of entrance gate for the garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 287
    - Detail of entrance steps for Residence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 288
    - Details of walls, balustrade, etc., Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 289
    - 1/2" scale details of Garden, 1915 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 290
    - Topographical survey, Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 291
    - Plan of garden on Dining room axis, 1916 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 292
    - General arrangement plan, Undated (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 293
    - Details of garden, Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 294
    - Detail of steps and entrance gate, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 295
    - Lattice enclosure for Residence, 1916 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 296
    - One eighth inch scale plan of Landscape work, by Architect Vernon Redding, Undated (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 297
    - General arrangement plan, Undated (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 298
    - Plan of pool and paved area, 1/2" scale details of garden, 1915 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 299
    - General working plan for garden, 1916 (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 300
    - Details of Pool and Arbor, 1916 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 301
    - 1/2" scale details of Garden, 1915 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 302
    - Diagrammatic planting arrangement, 1916 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 303
    - Diagrammatic planting arrangement, 1916 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 304
  - Nelson, C. L. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Main entrance steps and Terraces for Residence, Undated (Box 8)
      Sheet # 175
    - Revised main entrance steps and terrace, 1913 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 176
    - Topographic plan of property (McDonald & Dodd, Architects), 1911 (Box 8)
      Sheet # 177
    - Topographic plan of property, Undated (Box 8)
      Sheet # 178
    - Floor plans of Residence (McDonald & Dodd, Architects), 1911 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 179
    - Topographic plan of Property, Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 180
    - Topographical plan of property (McDonald & Dodd, Architects), 1911 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 181
    - Grading Plan, 1912 (Folder 13)
      Sheet # 187
    - Plan for Walk and Steps, 1913 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 188
    - Foundation plan, by Architects N. M. Woods (Memphis), Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 189
    - Revised main entrance steps and terraces, 1913 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 190
    - Main entrance steps and terraces, Undated (Folder 13)
      Sheet # 191
    - General plan of arrangement, Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 192
      Format: Watercolor on Mylar
    - General plan of arrangement, Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 193
    - Sketch plan of Entry walk, Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 194
    - Revised main entry steps and terraces, 1913 (Box 11)
      Sheet # 195
    - Typed specifications for landscape work - 2 copies with total of 8 pages, 1912 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 196
    - Sketch of Property arrangement, Undated (Box 11)
      Sheet # 197
    - Rough sketch of Site Plan, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 198
    - Rough sketch of Site Plan, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 199
    - Rough sketch of Site Plan, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 200
    - Rough sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 201
    - Study of main entrance steps and terraces, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 202
    - Study of Terrace, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 203
    - Revised Terrace plan, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 204
    - Rough sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 205
    - Suggestion for Addition to House Plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 206
    - Sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 207
    - Staking plan, Location of house, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 208
    - Sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 209
    - Sketch of Master bedroom and Dressing area, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 210
    - Arrangement of Suite - Master and Guest bedrooms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 211
    - Sketch of Floor plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 212
    - Arrangement of Suite, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 213
    - Revision of Terrace, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 214
    - Perspective Sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 215
    - Plan for Walk and Steps, 1913 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 216
    - Floor plan by Architects N. M. Woods "void" " penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 217
    - Revised main entrance steps and terraces, 1913 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 218
    - Detailed perspective sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 219
    - Main entrance steps and terraces, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 220
      Format: Blueprint with crayon revisions